# **GEORGE HU**

## Junior Front-End Web Developer

## **CONTACT**

≥ 25 Abilene Ct, Richmond Hill, ON, L4C 0S5

- ① 647-866-5182
- ngeorge.hu.ottawa@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

## Languages

JavaScript, TypeScript, Java Python, HTML/CSS

#### Libraries

React, Redux, Vue.js,

#### **Databases**

MySQL, MongoDB,

#### CI/CD

Git, Docker

#### Other

Axios, Webpack, Node.js, Express, Rest APIs Google Cloud Platform Linux, Docker

### **PROFILE**

Front End Developer with 2 years experiences on web development. Experienced in object-oriented programing; developing, testing and debugging code; designing interfaces. Highly motivated individual dedicated to writing clear, concise, robust code that works. Striving to never stop learning and improving.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Loveonly Inc. Ontario/ Junior Web developer

2019 - 2021

- Designed, developed and modified a single page application of administration management system using React, Ant Design, Axios, webpack and other technologies.
- Collaborated with 2 different development teams to build a diamond booking website using Vue, Mint-UI, Axios, Webpack, Google Maps API and other technologies for front-end application, and Node, Express and MongoDB for back-end application
- Analyzed systems flow, data usage, and work processes; investigated problem areas
- Suggested 10+ improvements to product design and functionality as informed by user-experience reporting
- Collaborated with client service teams to understand and solve bottlenecks such as storage solutions and proposed feature expansions
- Documented technical specifications and dependencies of applications

## Megafoam Inc, Ontario / Product Designer

2015 - 2019

- Created 3D models for Automotive injection foam gaskets and applied strength analysis for the material
- Communicated with program manager, salesman, costumers and tool maker closely to test and update automobile products

## University of Ottawa / Researcher

2012 - 2015

- Designed a mobile robot control system for complicated environment navigation using Python
- Created a data fusion algorithm for mobile robots sensors using Dempster-Shafer theory
- Analyzed and combined the data and simulated the robot's moving trajectories in Matlab

## **EDUCATION**

## Master of Applied Science in Mechanical Engineering,

University of Ottawa, Canada

2014.11

**Bachelor of Engineering (Automation)** 

Anhui University of Technology, China

2011.07

Certification-Data Science with Python, we clouddata.com

Complete SQL Mastery, codewithmosh.com

**Publication**-"Human Friendly Autonomous Robot using Dempster-Shafer Sensor Fusion"

International Council of the Aeronautical Sciences, 2015